{"data":[{"question":"One of the most difficult problems in understanding sleep is determining what the functions of sleep is.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"most ","b":"in understanding ","c":"determining ","d":"is","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Is understanding-> is to understand","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Teaching and learning are part of the same educational experience but unfortunately they are often thought of to be separate.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are part ","b":"the same ","c":"are often thought ","d":"to be separate","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n-To be separate-> being separated","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"An epigram is usually defined to be a bright or witty thought tersely and ingeniously expressed.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"usually ","b":"to be ","c":"or ","d":"ingeniously ","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To be-> as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"We usually define an epigram to be a bright or witty thought tersely and ingeniously expressed.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"an epigram ","b":"to be ","c":"tersely and ingeniously ","d":"expressed","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To be-> as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Perhaps you have found some words to live by and treasured them because they say something which you regard to be vital. \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to live by ","b":"treasured ","c":"something ","d":"to be ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- To be-> as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Imagine to my surprise when I saw one man tn the car pull out a pocket book and begin to read.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to my surprise ","b":"when ","c":"pull out ","d":"to read","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- To my suprise-> how I was suprise\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"To read Tolstoy and to be introduced to nineteenth-century Russian literature is two excellent reasons for taking professor Morrel's course.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to be ","b":"to ","c":"is ","d":"for taking ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Is-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Paris is one of the many cities in the world that are currently developing programs of restoring their historical buildings.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is ","b":"are currently ","c":"of restoring ","d":"their ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Of restoring-> to restore","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Ballads were early types of poetry and may have been among a first kinds of music.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were early ","b":"poetry ","c":"a ","d":"music","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- A-> the","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"During the 1600's skilled shoemakers scarce were in what is now the United States.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"skilled ","b":"shoemakers ","c":"scarce were ","d":"what is ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Scarce were-> scarcity was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"}]}